One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let us go shining! Running! Forever!
We have to push forward!
Bonds that never change will surely
illuminate the far end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass! We are best friends.
We are the ones who will clear our own path from here on.
On days where we will sprint with all we've got. Go east, go west.
We will find them one by one, achieve all the things we want to do.
I can not wait for the morning, I am aching to go!
If that is how it is, then onwards: to the sun! The sky!
Drag yourself up and go, go, go!
That is right! Shining! Running! Forever!
Combine the pieces of your dream into one.
If it feels right then that is your treasure.
Let us go shining! Running! Forever!
We have to push forward!
Bonds that never change will surely
illuminate the far end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
I'll engulf you in darkness, Straw Hat!
You won't defeat me! I'm the guy who will find One Piece and become the Pirate King!
Every challenge we surpass brings the possibility of thrills.
Tomorrow and the days beyond will form
a powerful, passionate chain of excitement!
That is right! Shining! Running! Forever!
Leave it up to your curiosity, follow your emotions.
To the place you seek, that's the adventure!
Let us go shining! Running! Forever!
Spread open your heart's map
and the power of your bonds will definitely
seize the limits of our dreams.
Never! Never! Never! Never stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Arriving at Dressrosa!
The Country of Passion, Love, and Toys!
All tall waves were originally...
...little waves, barely worthy of notice.
Hey! What's gonna happen to the arms deal between the Donquixote family and us!?
I've been trying to reach them
but no one is picking up!
What should we do?!
I-I can't believe this!
We will lose the war without arms!
Hey, hey, listen to this!
Those reckless rookies from two years ago formed an alliance!
I'm sure they're up to something!
Doflamingo resigned from the Warlords of the Sea!
Why did he do that?!
Isn't there anymore information?!
How did they find out about our alliance?!
New World: Kid Pirate Crew's Hideout
Who is this freelance writer named Absa?!
He gets scoops very often these days!
I don't care about us.
I'm more concerned about the other news.
Straw Hat and Trafalgar!
I'm sure they're looking to take out
one of the Four Emperors like we are.
Which one is their target!?
Your highness!
Dressrosa
It's me.
I resigned from the Warlords of the Sea.
--He picked up!
--Picked up!
Doflamingo!?
He will hear you!
Hello? I'm Monkey D. Luffy!
I'm gonna become the Pirate King!
I told you to shut up!
Hey, Mingo!
So you're that idiot Caesar's boss!?
That bastard hurt Brownbeard and the kids!
We will give you back Caesar as we promised but if you do that again,
I will beat the hell out of you!
Straw Hat Luffy.
You went away for 2 years
after your brother died.
Where were you
and what were you doing?
I shouldn't tell anyone about it!
I wanted to see you.
What?
I have something
that you'll want very badly now.
H-Hey!
How delicious is that meat
you're talking about?!
Straw Hat-ya!
Don't get drawn into his pace!
One chunk of meat! Two chunks of meat!
Luffy!
Keep yourself together!
This is a special attack called "His Pace"!
Joker! Cut the crap!
We'll hand Caesar over to you as we promised.
Well, that's for your own good.
If you try to run away with him,
you know what will happen to you guys.
Now, can I hear my precious
business partner's voice?
Joker! I'm sorry!
You resigned from the Warlords of the Sea for me!
8 hours from now,
at the beach on the southeast side of Green Bit,
the solitary island north of Dressrosa.
We will leave Caesar there
at 3 in the afternoon.
Go ahead and pick him up.
And this will all be finished.
That's too bad.
I wish I could have a drink with you...
Just hang up!
That was close.
You almost got drawn into his pace.
Your eyes! Your eyes!
Hey, wait!
We didn't tell him how many men he can bring!
"How many men"?
What are we gonna do
if he brings his entire crew?!
It doesn't matter.
The handover of Caesar is a part of our plan. It's just to lure them.
You mean, destroying the SMILE factory while it's unguarded is our main purpose?
Yes, but we don't know where it is.
You're joking.
Don't worry!
Factories are big. You can barely miss them.
Once we get there, we'll super find it!
I will destroy it with my laser beam!
Big bro!
I have intelligence on
everything but the factory.
No wonder.
It's an important asset for them, isn't it?
Maybe there is a secret to it.
Law-dono!
You said you're going to
go to Green Bit earlier!
We will dock this ship at Dressrosa. Don't worry.
Tora-guy, have you been to that island?
Dress-roba!
Roba: Old Lady
It's "rosa"!
I've never been there.
It's that bastard's kingdom.
Then, let's figure everything out once we get there!
It's gonna be an adventure!
Can't wait to see Dressrosa!
I wanna go to the Wano Country soon, too!
Don't be ridiculous!
You can't just show up without a plan...
Sanji, I'm hungry!
What's for breakfast?
Sandwiches.
Yeah! I want a cotton-candy sandwich!
I'll just have a cup of tea.
I don't like bread!
I can't tell you why we were being chased.
But we set sail for the place called Zou originally.
Zou?
Do you know it?
It's another coincidence.
After handing over Caesar
and destroying the SMILE factory,
I was gonna head for Zou.
My crew is there.
I-If so, can we go along with you there?
Yes, you can! Let's go there
and then the Wano Country!
Hey!
3 Samurai including me and Momonosuke...
4 of us headed for Zou.
but our ship wrecked...
and two of us Samurai and Momonosuke drifted to Dressrosa.
But we had been chased by
Doflamingo and the others there
and I ran into an unknown ship.
There, I met the children
who were looking to get treated.
And unfortunately, the ship left the port
before I knew it and headed for that island.
--Father!
--Oh no! Momonosuke!
I was gonna go after the ship...
and my fellow samurai Kanjuro tried to cover me but got caught!
Go after Momonosuke! Don't worry about me!
He let me sail out to the sea!
I have to save him!
I have to go back!
What a man, that Kanjuro!
Kanjuro!
Alright! I'm gonna go save him with you!
Guys! Don't forget our purpose!
New World
Near the Red Line
Navy Headquarters
There are only seven Warlords of the Sea in the world!
They are the pirates who were chosen and given...
the carte blanche for robbery by the World Government
in exchange for their overwhelming strength and notorious prestige!
Them taking sides with the Government has to be...
seen as a threat to all
other pirates in the world.
The greatest swordsman in the world...
Hawk-Eyes, Dracule Mihawk.
The king of Dressrosa and a charismatic devil...
The Heavenly Demon, Donquixote Doflamingo.
He is now the Navy's human weapon!
The Tyrant, Bartholomew Kuma.
The empress of Amazon Lily...
The Pirate Empress, Boa Hancock.
One of the Worst Generation
and the mastermind of the Rocky Port Incident...
The Surgeon of Death, Trafalgar Law!
The leader of the Pirate Dispatch Organization and a living legend...
The Thousand Piece Clown, Buggy!
And with the man I told you about earlier, they make up for the Seven Warlords.
But that all changed early this morning.
Doflamingo resigned out of the blue.
And we might need to expel Law from the Warlords depending on his intention.
The third great power, that stands alongside Navy HQ and the Four Emperors, cannot remain this unstable.
Yes, I know, Brannew.
Fleet Admiral!
I'm not gonna let Law and
Straw Hat do whatever they want!
I got an annoying call from
Smoker of the G-5 yesterday.
Let's see how things go for today.
I've sent Fujitora!
Fujitora: Wisteria Tiger
Your Majesty!
Dressrosa
Please don't quit!
Trébol-sama, where are you?!
Have you seen Trébol-sama?
No.
I wonder what Young
Master-sama is going to do?!
If the Navy is gonna come to attack, I want to fight-in!
We will just follow the Young Master.
Oh, Baby 5!
What are you doing up there?!
Look! The whole kingdom is going crazy!
I'm sure the whole world is getting upset!
Hey, hey!
By the way, did you get
your fiancé killed again?
Too close!
Why do you keep asking me that?
You're so annoying!
Annoying but?
--Too close!
Annoying but what? Hmmm?
Annoying but you like me, maybe?
That's enough!
Young Master-sama was calling you!
He wanted you to bring that thing!
Stay away! You make me sick!
Hey, hey, hey!
You just keep getting your fiancé killed! Baby 5!
Stop choosing guys that will
be killed by Doffy and marry me!
Hmm, just kidding!
Do you...
...need me?
Cut it out!
The Colosseum is always packed.
Thanks to you, Diamante.
What are you saying?
Doffy, that's because
you're a charismatic king.
No.
That's because you're strong.
Stop. You make it sound like
I'm the hero of the Colosseum.
You are the hero of the Colosseum.
Stop saying that.
Okay, I'll stop.
Alright, I admit it if you insist!
Yes, I am the hero of the Colosseum!
I brought it!
Doffy, it's that thing!
You're too close!
Too close, but...?
But I like it. Sit down.
If Straw Hat Luffy finds out about this,
I'm sure he will try to get hold of it.
An alliance can sometimes prove a hindrance.
Diamante. I want to entrust this to you.
Wait a second, Doffy! I can't take it.
No, I want to entrust this to you.
Stop. You make it sound like
I'm some kind of genius.
I can only entrust this to a genius like you.
Stop saying that.
Okay, I'll stop.
Alright, I'll admit that I'm
a genius if you insist!
Yes! I can take care of
that dumb-ass Straw Hat!
I'll be counting on you!
I know he will jump at it!
His older brother's power, the Flame Fruit.
I'm sure he wouldn't want
anybody else to have it!
The island has come into view.
What is that rocky island?!
We made it! It's Dressrosa!
You idiot! Don't shout!
Doflamingo will hear us!
No, he won't!
We'll save you soon, Kanjuro!
This is a kingdom of love
and passion - Dressrosa.
Shores of Dressrosa
We made it! Dressrosa!
I said you're too loud, Luffy!
We're in their territory now!
This week, I'm...
...super!
I'm gonna find the factory right away and ka-boom!
Hey! I just had a good idea!
Momo!
Fly!
You're too heavy! Get off of me!
I can't fly and I'm not
gonna enter the island!
My father told me not to!
You can't fly?! What are you talking about?!
I saw you flying!
I don't know what you're talking about!
I said I can't!
I really saw him flying!
But he doesn't have wings.
See? I told you!
I don't remember flying!
E-Even if I did fly...
What's your name?
I-I'll never do such a dreadful thing again!
I'm not gonna fly in the sky!
Huh? Are you scared of heights?
You bastard!
Ouch!
Don't disrespect me!
We warriors don't get scared of anything!
Ow, ow, ow... You!
Stop it, you fool!
Luffy-san, he's an eight-year old...
Cut the "warrior" crap!
I'm gonna become the Pirate King one day, you idiot!
I'm gonna become the shogun
of the Wano Country someday, you fool!
What did you say?! You eel!
You're so arrogant! You monkey!
Who did you call "monkey"?!
You're being rude to a monkey!
Enough, Momonosuke!
He saved us!
I'm sorry, Luffy-dono. Please forgive him.
Even though he's a child,
he's a proud warrior of the Wano Country.
Having said that,
I can't believe you take an
8-year old so seriously!
I don't like cowards! Idiot!
You...
Dammit!
--Oh, Nami!
--Yes, yes! Momo-chan, come here!
That monkey is...
Get off her!
What's their problem?
Like father, like son!
I didn't know warriors were so sick!
H-How dare you say that!
Hey, Kin'emon! Let's go to the town already!
How should we change
our clothes for a disguise?
Oh yeah!
This is how people dress in Dressrosa.
For women, nothing For men, collared shirts
Let me change you all so you can fit in!
Dressrosa is the best!
Yeah!
Stop lying!
Hey.
I want you to keep this.
Is this a Vivre Card?
It'll point toward the island called Zou
that I talked about earlier.
If anything happens to us, go straight there!
W-What do you mean "Anything happens"?
Nothing will happen, right?
Who knows.
This is a map that my crewmate drew.
Wow! So terribly drawn!
We're here now, at the
west coast of Dressrosa.
We, the Caesar Handover Team, will...
Current Location
...go across Dressrosa and
cross the very long bridge to north
and get to Green Bit.
Why do we have to go across Dressrosa?
We can just take the ship!
All of us together!
I heard it's impossible to travel by water.
Oh, that sounds interesting.
P-Please get me there safely!
And you all, the Sunny's Security Team,
should watch out for the enemy's attack.
Don't let them take the ship!
--What?! What do you mean by that?!
Kanjuro... I hope he's still alive.
What?! I thought guarding
the ship was the safest!
Guys, we're in the enemy's stronghold.
But we're with Sanji so...
Huh?! Sanji's not here!
I mean, Luffy and the others are gone, too!
They're the key to this plan!
Where did they go?!
Hey! Who's gonna protect us?!
Visitors to this kingdom are fascinated by a number of things.
First, by the fragrantly-scented flowers
and the delicious smell of local food.
Smells good!
Second,
the tireless, passionate
dancing of the local women.
Smells lovely!
And another thing...
Hey! Wait! Give it back!
Wait! Mario! Hey!
Give me my arm back!
Boy! You're a bad dog!
The cotton's gonna fall out!
Wait!
No!
I got a side stitch!
Although there's only cotton inside!
S-Stuffed toys?!
A shocking surprise for all visitors to this kingdom.
Hello!
I am a soldier!
Oh? Have we met before?
Your faces look familiar.
Oh, yeah!
You were in the paper this morning...
Ouch!
Oh no! The strings got tangled up! Help me!
What's this?! A toy?!
Everywhere you look,
blending in with the town...
and living side-by-side with humans.
They are living toys.
This is a kingdom of love
and passion and toys.
The port town - Acacia.
A man has been stabbed!
Oh, again?
What do you mean "Again"?
Is there a phantom slasher or something?
No. Women in this country are passionate about love and most are the jealous type.
So when a man cheats on a woman,
things can get pretty violent.
How scary!
The more beautiful they are, the more likely to stab a man!
Toys are moving by themselves but that's okay!
Let's eat!
I don't have time to fool around like this!
I need to look for Kanjuro
as soon as possible!
Whoa-whoa, relax.
I know we need to hurry but it's better to get some information rather than just run everywhere.
Isn't it strange?
Their king just abdicated from the throne this morning.
I thought there would be more confusion.
Maybe they don't know yet.
No way.
Let's ask. Hey, pops!
Don't!
What's your problem?!
You were on the front page of
the newspaper this morning!
Here's your order.
Thank you for waiting...
...or not!
Here it comes!
I couldn't wait any longer!
Dress Shrimp Paella!
Rose Squid Ink Pasta!
And Fairy Pumpkin Gazpacho!
Everything looks yummy!
Let's eat!
Yum-yum!
What's "Fairy Pumpkin"?
Um, that's... In this country,
we still believe in a myth about fairies!
Or not!
Well, people claim to see fairies! Or not!
Seeing fairies?
Yes! Isn't it interesting?
For centuries!
Even though most of us haven't
seen them, they do exist.
People call those fairies...
..."guardian deities of Dressrosa"!
Or not!
Ah, shut up!
He got it right again! Fourteen times in a row!
What's going on?
It's a little noisy back there.
It's a roulette game.
Okay, white!
Let's see.
How does it go? What is it?
You've missed it again. It's black 20!
It should be white this time!
It's black again!
That's awful!
They're a disgrace to Donquixote!
I guess I'm running out
of luck. This is no good.
What do you wanna do? Do you wanna quit?
We can make a lot of money
when Buffalo-san isn't here.
No.
One last time.
I bet everything!
Great!
Then I'm gonna bet everything
on whichever color you don't pick.
Let's play it like real men!
Everything? Really?
Yeah.
Alright, let's do it.
Place your bets!
White, please!
If you pick white, I bet on black, of course!
Come on, white! White!
Which is it?
I'm sorry, old man!
--It's bl...
--White!
Ah?! Who the hell are you?!
Look carefully! It's black, idiot!
It's white.
Old man, you win!
What?!
You bastard! Stay out of it!
That's right!
Do you wanna get your ass kicked?!
Who is he?
Doesn't he have any idea who they are?!
He got himself involved, as usual!
D-Do I really win?!
Yeah, you win.
I don't know who you are
but thank you for your kindness!
Don't mention it. I just said what I saw.
I'm happy for you.
But, old man, you look so strong...
What you're doing is so senseless, you brat!
When we say "It's black," it's black!
He can't see anyway so it doesn't matter!
You're so annoying!
Go away!
Young man, could you step aside a little bit?
I'm going to send those people to hell.
It's heavy! So heavy...
I-I'm going to get crushed!
What?! What's wrong with him?!
What did he do?!
Wow! It left a hole!
It's not too bad being blind.
I know there are many hideous things
that are better unseen.
Translation & initial timing, Crunchyroll
Timing, Galaxy 9000, , Time-checking, Sewil
Quality-checking, Sewil, Galaxy 9000, Feeso
Soundtracking, Halee
Video editing, Sewil
Raw provider, Crunchyroll
Scroll infobox artist, sergiart.deviantart.com